# HANFANG CHENG (ANNA)

### RECENT GRADUATE | JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

#### **PROFILE**

Have at least 1-year experience in web development. I enjoy coding because I like the lifestyle it brings me. Recently, I have been improving and gaining more knowledge of my **React** and frontend-related libraries, such as **TailwindCSS** and problem-solving skills, for a couple of months. I hope that one day, I can become a professional web developer to create good-quality web/apps and help people solve their problems and needs.

Github -> https://github.com/anna0625/

LinkedIn -> https://www.linkedin.com/in/annacheng625/

Factor Trait Report of me -> <a href="https://github.com/anna0625/anna0625/blob/main/factor-trait-report\_hanfang-cheng.pdf">https://github.com/anna0625/anna0625/blob/main/factor-trait-report\_hanfang-cheng.pdf</a>

# **UNI PROJECTS | ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

MOTION MANAGEMENT SURVEY - DATA VISUALISATION
AUSTRALIAN CLINICAL DOSIMETRY SERVICE, 03/2022-06/2022

Collaborated with team of five to develop a web portal that can visualise and export the data of MM survey by using **Next.js & TailwindCSS**.

I was responsible for some charts' interaction functionality, such as group-by and select box, and data analysis on the website. (Demo)

PARTICIPATION OF CIS - MISGA CASE COMPETITION 2020 (The Certificate)

# TEAMWORK AWARD - TAIWAN SUMMER OF CODE 2018

ITSA 教育部智慧創新人才培育計畫

Collaborated with team of four in the development of SuccuBook (one of the graduation project). (Demo)

### TWO GRADUATION PROJECTS

PROVIDENCE UNIVERSITY, 08/2017-12/2018

Collaborated with team of four in the developments.

- RoseFit an IOT plant-caring system.
   I was responsible for the front-end web development using PHP & MySQL, and the database design and management.
- SuccuBook a website of succulent identification.
   I was responsible for the back-end using **TensorFlow transfer learning** model.

# **LANGUAGES**

English (Professional working proficiency) | Mandarin (Native) | Taiwanese (Good)



#### **SKILLS**

I have some experience in:

- \* [Web] => HTML5 & CSS3 & JS | React | TailwindCSS
- \* [Languages] => Python & Java
- \* [Database & Hosting] => Firebase | SQL / MySQL
- \* [Tools & Others] => Git/Github | Agile Methodology | Adobe Lightroom

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### COMPILER TEACHING ASSISTANT

PROVIDENCE UNIVERSITY, TAIWAN - 02/2019-06/2019

Assisted the teacher with classroom management and document coordination to maintain positive learning environment. Delivered personalised educational, behavioural and emotional support to individual students to enable positive learning outcomes.

### PROGRAMMING TEACHING ASSISTANT (JAVA)

PROVIDENCE UNIVERSITY, TAIWAN - 09/2016-06/2017

Assisted teachers with classroom management and document coordination to maintain positive learning environment. Assisted students with **problem-solving** of class materials in basic **Java**. Delivered personalised educational, behavioural and emotional support to individual students to enable positive learning outcomes.

### WEB SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR

PROVIDENCE UNIVERSITY - 09/2016-05/2017

Experienced the usage of different operating systems, such as FreeBSD, **Linux**. Collaborated with other students and provided ongoing efficiency and security maintenance and patching on website interface to maintain viability after launch.

# **EDUCATION**

Master of Information Technology, 2020-2022 University of Melbourne, Australia

Bachelor of Computer Science 2015-2019

Providence University, Taiwan

# **REFERENCES**

Irene Lee

Developer working in Seek 0478977625 | irene.lee0905@gmail.com

### Ocha

Supervisor of motion management survey - data visualisation 0411220812 | ocha.cakramurti@unimelb.edu.au